And that one goes there.
Oh, I don't know where to put that.
Oh, I didn't see you there.
Hey, welcome.
Today is a very special day because it is Friday.
And yeah.
Cheers.
That is the sweet taste of Friday.
Oh yeah.
Amazing.
Anyway, I'm getting annoyed by this guy knocking on the door.
Sir, beat it.
Peace and quiet.
Now, I was doing things last time and people had a party.
It was a great party.
But that's all about what happened.
Because I spent a lot of time building things.
But today, I'm gonna do that again, I think.
Dude, I had such a blast last time with this game.
That was so nice.
Honestly, I don't know what to do today.
I'll see what happens when it happens.
And look at that.
Soli the Cool Slime.
Now, that is the coolest slime ever.
Hanging out in one of the coolest buildings ever.
Look at how that looks, huh?
I made that last time.
Beautiful stuff.
Now, the bucket was, unfortunately, not of very much use.
I was hoping that I could take the magic liquid and scoop it up and then pour it where I want it to be poured.
Unfortunately, that's not how the cookie crumbles.
Loot all this and deposit all that.
And let me see here.
I really like this home right here, but part of me wants to slim this down a bit.
Maybe make this place more of a utility area and have people move to various parts of the world.
You know, like the beach and the snowy region, the jungle, all the different places.
It's gonna be great.
Sort this, please.
First off, where's my potions there?
Let's just put all the potions in here for now.
That's not a potion.
It looks like a potion, but it's not.
Restoration, obsidian, all this goes in here.
And then I decide what I want after I put it all in.
That's the plan.
The spiky ball, you know what?
Let me sell some stuff.
Uh, I guess Hano is gone, unfortunately.
So, Ludo, how about you?
Will you buy my things?
Will you buy spiky ball?
Silt, nice.
Scoop up a small amount of liquid.
Yeah.
It gives one def... Wait.
Oh, wait.
I didn't even realize you could do that.
Maybe I did it once and forgot, I don't know.
Atiki torch.
The pylons!
I need to do that today, man.
I need to link everything.
What is, uh, doing that?
That's this guy over here again.
Can you please leave me alone?
Now, last time we had a no death stream.
That was amazing.
And you know what?
We're gonna do it again.
I feel so relieved.
I finally had a no death stream.
So nice.
Um, what do I want to do here?
Topaz gem corn?
Wait a minute!
Hold on a second now.
What?
Where did I get this?
I don't... I have no memory of this.
What did I... What?
Let's put this here.
Wait, I can't.
Oh, is this a desert thing?
It's yellow.
Maybe it's a desert thing.
Oh, I want to try this today.
The... the defense force or whatever, the waves.
Let's see here.
Oh, also, I did make a potion.
I remember this now.
I made a potion of crate.
Somewhere.
Did I not?
Is it in here?
Well, there's actually a bunch of things in there.
Oh yeah, white!
Royal gel.
Slimes become friendly.
That one, um...
You know what?
I guess the thing I can do is to have it here and then just do that.
You know, this is a nice way to... Oh my god, this is way better than what I did before.
How did I not realize this?
What the fuck?
This is amazing.
I'm an idiot.
Why have I been carrying them around here?
Oh well.
Delete that one.
Let's delete this little tiny piece of palm wood.
The aether torch.
Let's see how that looks.
Very aether-like.
Whatever that means.
Let's do the silt.
There it is.
I wonder if there's a chance to get something really rare by depositing the silt into the extractor.
Would be fun.
Put everything in.
I need a bigger storage room.
Maybe I will expand the storage room to the right here and make one huge one.
And not only that, but put it at the bottom.
Maybe have a storage shack.
Oh!
Even better, a storage cellar.
Maybe that's what I need to do.
And because I spawn over here every time, maybe I should put it here.
Wouldn't this make the most sense?
Hold on now.
I have many things I want to do today.
I have so many plans, and I'm in no rush to do any of it.
And that feels amazing.
I want to do pylons.
I want to make people happy.
I want to acquire all the items.
Oh wait, I planted this.
I'm an idiot.
No wait, I didn't.
Did I?
What did I just... Shit, I think I just destroyed something rare.
Rid of that one.
Wait, the tree statue?
Right, I also made a little hut here.
Look at this.
Isn't this neat?
Look at that.
That looks so good.
Except these little parts here.
I'm not quite sure how to fix that yet.
But maybe I'll get it later.
And there's a little owl sitting on the roof as well.
This is fantastic.
We should mow the grass, because that means no more enemies will spawn.
Get away.
Let's just mow all of this.
Now, see, this is the point where I should have kept my thingy.
Oh, I can also destroy it with spells.
Never mind.
This is awesome.
Get rid of that grass.
Mow the lawn, so we can keep these kits off of it.
Okay, there we go.
This looks better.
Very nice.
Remove that one.
Get away.
Wait a minute, the gels are friendly.
They're not, but they will be.
There we go.
This one I always want, honestly.
Can I...
Maybe I'll exchange this one for that.
Something like that.
I don't know.
Cool.
Get rid of these.
These are never gonna grow, because if they haven't grown yet, it's not gonna happen.
That's my take on that.
Oh, you know what?
Let me grab my bug in it.
Because there are things that I want to grab at my house location that I'm building, by the way.
Which I want to finish today, because I have big plans with that as well.
Is it in weapons?
It is.
Makes so much sense.
Why do I have an extra one of these?
That's what I don't understand.
Did I buy two of them by accident?
Or is it on accident or by accident?
I'm not sure.
I can sell it for a lot of money.
Here you go, buddy.
That's for you.
The tool belt.
Um, let's put this here.
Also, is it gonna show me...
Wait, what just happened?
Oh, he's throwing bottles!
That's his attack, I guess.
Alright then, sir.
Now, did I get anything special last time that I need to check with... What's his name now?
Bradley?
I don't know, maybe.
You know what?
I should make a home just for Bradley.
Bradley, and maybe one other person.
So we have a pylon here.
Let me see where that connects.
I can go to the desert pylon.
I never figured out the pylon over here.
I did have three people move in.
Fjell, Sparkle, and Izzy.
Unfortunately, it didn't work just yet, and I'm not sure why that is.
Let me ask Bradley about it.
Maybe he'll tell me.
I hear a race of lizard men live in the jungle.
Maybe you can get the attention of one by felling a giant beast of the jungle.
Yeah, see, I want to do this.
You know what?
Let me write that down.
Actually, let me be strategic about this now.
List of things to do in this game.
I'm gonna write, uh, defeat giant beast of the jungle.
Okay.
Nice.
Construct pylons.
Okay, that's it for now.
I will add to that list later.
Thank you.
Now tell me more.
You met a stylist.
She went off adventuring.
Have I met the stylist?
None of these are stylists, right?
Okay, on the ground.
So, she's somewhere down there.
If Seymour's wares don't interest you, a wandering merchant... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not all of the undead monsters are hostile.
I hear one even sells merchandise deep on the ground.
I'm not sure I have found this.
I have found Fjell, who is a goblin, I think.
Does he qualify as an undead monster?
If you thought rainy days were a drag, wait till you see it.
Yeah, I've seen it.
And I've seen the king of it.
Beautiful lanterns.
Celebrate your victories.
I wonder wishing you good fortune if that gives me a buff.
Well, I don't have it now, but yeah.
Empty bottle.
Okay, yeah, I want to explore the snow biome a bit more as well.
I want to make an iglo.
Antlion tunnels.
I have found a marble biome.
I say that these locations are inhabited by some very dangerous creatures.
Wait, granite biomes?
I think I've seen this before.
Yeah.
Many treasures in the jungle.
I feel like there's stuff in the jungle that I need to see.
The underworld is made of a material called hellstone.
So it's actually called the underworld.
Amazing.
When you are ready to challenge the keeper of the underworld, you will have to make a living sacrifice.
Yeah.
He is the keeper of the underworld, huh?
Is there anything I can tell me about how to get into that one temple that I saw?
This place on the ground, man.
Not that.
Try to gather some obsidian.
I have done that.
Some say there are giant beehives buried underground in the jungle.
Again, the jungle.
Things are happening in the jungle.
In the middle of the night, on snowy evenings, a terrifying roaring sound comes from the wilderness.
Something is out there.
In the middle of the night, on snowy evenings.
Okay.
So I got to go to the snowy biome in the middle of the night when it snows.
I hear a race of lizard men living in the jungle.
Yeah, are we just resetting here?
Okay, gotcha.
We checked everything.
We are up to date.
The Tiki torch, delete that shit.
I don't want it.
Now, this eternal crystal thingy, let's put it on the ground somewhere.
Oh, we can't just put it anywhere, unfortunately.
Put it here for now.
Now, you know what?
This goes in miscellaneous.
Miscellaneous.
Put this here, stack it up.
There we go.
Now, pink gel.
Miscellaneous.
Miscellaneous is a very terrible thing to start doing, you know, because everything starts to become miscellaneous.
It's a tricky trap to fall into.
Seashells, I believe they are... actually, they are materials.
Hold on.
Have I asked you about this, Bradley?
Reef block.
And shell piles.
What is the point of this?
Have you... you know what?
Let's make shell piles.
I need to see what the point of this is.
Make a bunch.
Let's see here.
I mean, okay.
Looks kind of cool, I guess.
You could use it for something.
Is that a button?
Oh, it's a pressure plate.
Oh, and also this?
Honey dispenser.
Can be placed.
I never figured this out.
You know what?
Let's put this in a house in the jungle.
Huh?
Apparently, there's a beehive there, so we got to find that as well, by the way.
This is the place I want to get into.
And I have no idea how to do it.
I sort of excavated all the way around, trying to find a way in.
This seemed like the way in, but it was sort of locked by a door.
At least had the chest.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
Maybe I need to defeat the king of the jungle or whatever he called it.
Gain the respect of the lizard man, right?
That's how I'm going to get in here.
So I need to find a boss down here, I think.
Some kind of boss.
A show.
Yeah.
All right.
What else can I put in my chest here?
Is this about Enchi now?
Yeah.
Workbench.
Just take all this.
Nice.
Finally, this is empty.
Now I can deposit my money.
That always stays in here for safety reasons.
And oh, there's something I want to do, by the way.
Let me see if I remember this.
What do I need to make this?
Was it... There was a void bag, remember?
I want to check that out.
But I forgot how to make it.
Hold on.
Fuck, what could it have been made of?
Silk, I guess?
Hold on, let me check silk.
I think I'm right.
Show me.
Let's see here.
Man, there's a bunch of stuff.
What looks like a bag here?
I'm not... Nope.
No, no, no, nope.
So many different vanity items.
No, it's not here.
Shit, it's somewhere else.
Maybe it's ores?
Let's see.
Let me try Tissue Sample, Hellstone, Hellstone Bar.
Probably Hellstone doesn't do anything.
Obsidian.
Obsidian probably, actually.
It had like a purple color, I remember this.
Blueish purple.
Obsidian?
No, no, no, no.
Obsidian Toilet.
Wow.
Oh, that's cool.
Obsidian Chest.
Ooh, see, that would be a cool chest for weapons and stuff.
Dude, I have big plans.
Many plans.
What about Tissue?
Remind me about Tissue.
Oh no, pick it up.
There it is!
Void Bag.
So I have a Void Vault and a Void Bag.
Let me see here.
Summons the Void Vault, which is this one.
And the Void Vault, stored items can only be accessed by you.
Will contain items picked up by a Void Bag.
And the Void Bag functions as an extended inventory when open.
May pick up overflowing items when open.
See, that sounds incredible.
It sounds out of this world.
I think I can make this.
I need bones.
I have that.
I now need...
What?
What was the central one?
Ah, I forgot already.
God.
God damn.
Jungle Sp... Oh, Jungle Spores.
I have that.
How many do I have?
I forgot what the icon looked like.
Wait, is it here?
Oh, I have 41.
Dude, it's happening.
It's freaking... Oh wait, but I need to make two of them.
I need to make this one as well.
Oh, but it costs the same stuff.
Yes.
I can make it.
Is it just here?
Wait.
What do I need to...
Requires... Oh no!
What is that?
What is a Crimson?
Oh no, I thought I could make it.
Fuck!
What is a Crimson altar?
Hold on, what Crimson stuff do I have?
Let me actually check with Bradley here.
Crimson...
Crimson seeds I have?
I guess vertebra is also Crimson?
Let's see.
Here.
I guess vicious mushroom.
Oh man, I have so much shit in my inventory.
Delete this, delete this.
Quick, tell me about Crimson seeds.
Blood water spreads the Crimson.
Dude, can I choose to be evil in this game?
There's apparently a battle between this Crimson and the natural world, right?
AKA Rosalva, or what was the name?
The forest person.
I can either purify or I can spread Crimson.
I wonder if that's a choice later on to be evil.
What can I make with this?
Oh!
Oh, I thought this... Oh, this is just a vanity item.
Bloody spine.
Summons the brain of Cthulhu.
Summons the destroyer.
Man, how do I get Soul of Night?
I see this in all the big items.
Monster lasagna.
That right there is 100% genuine Ahamkara.
Trust.
I feel like a lot of these jokes are going over my head.
Gotta be honest here.
I'm not getting it.
Quick stack.
So, I clicked the button and everything moved away from my inventory.
And this guy was jumping at the same time and out of the corner of my eye it looked like he went boop, boop, my items went like this and away from me.
My god, I'm imagining things right now.
Remove the sandstone platform.
Oh, we got a blood moon.
Every fucking night is a blood moon.
Glass.
Let's put that in construction for now.
I'll deal with you later.
Actually, maybe I won't.
I can stand up here and chill.
The silk go in there.
Okay, so I really want to make that fucking void bag.
I'm gonna go explore the crimson again.
See if I can't find a crimson altar and bring it home.
Or at least something that will allow me to craft it.
Whatever.
Dude, this weapon is so good.
Dang.
I feel like I'm peeking with this weapon, honestly.
The only issue is that it doesn't penetrate.
So that is the one downside.
If this one was penetrating as well, boy, it would have been a good weapon.
Almost too good, maybe.
Okay.
Oh, I can actually close the door.
They're not gonna get inside.
Because I have the ultimate defense here.
I have a torch next to the door.
I discovered that's not gonna do anything.
Or it's not gonna make them enter, I mean.
Put this banner.
Do I already have one of these?
I'm running out of space for banners here.
Put it there.
Another shackle.
Boo.
I don't want shackle.
You know what?
I'm gonna put the sound at zero right now.
I don't want to hear them knocking on the door, because I just want to sort my inventory while this happens.
And then I'm gonna go out there when they're all stacked in the end and murder them all.
That's the plan.
I need to sell things.
Buy this rope.
I kind of want to sell this.
Yeah.
Sell this shit.
No, actually, no, no, no.
Take it back, take it back, take it back.
I regret my actions.
Oh, these two.
They are not belong there.
Here, buy this.
Okay.
Now, did I not have a potion of crate?
Oh, I did!
Here, there it is.
Wow.
I want to go fishing with this buff activated.
Maybe that's the first thing I'm gonna do here.
Also, why is there food in here?
It doesn't belong there.
Sort this.
This doesn't belong here either.
Let's put this in construction.
What do I have in here?
A bunch of work.
You know what?
Let's delete some stuff that I can always just craft again.
Kind of... I have so many hellforges.
What the hell?
Glass, wooden fence, boom, take it out of here.
I definitely need a chest just for blocks.
And then a construction chest that is for stuff like doors and, I don't know, glass.
You know, specialized things you made from the blocks.
That's the ultimate goal here.
The bucket goes in here.
I'm gonna do construction a little later, I think.
Now, I just kind of want to chill a bit.
So, what is this up here?
The banner chest.
I don't like the banner chest.
Banner chest makes me unhappy.
Wood,
mushrooms, goes here.
Oh, I already have bait, nice.
Bamboo.
What can I do with bamboo again?
Show me.
I mean, I can make some nice things.
A bamboo piano.
No, but I'm gonna save the bamboo.
No room here.
Shit, I'm running out of space.
You know what?
Get rid of this.
You know what I want to do, actually?
I just had an idea.
She sells seashells on the sea shore.
No, she sells all these kinds of redstone looking things, right?
I kind of want to experiment with this today as well.
Let me write that on my list.
Redstone experiments.
Experiments, nice.
I want to do that.
Okay, but not now.
I actually, you know what?
I've been craving some action.
I'm gonna go to Crimson and see if I can't find a Crimson Altar.
Maybe it's something that drops from the enemies and I need to be on the lookout.
Let me fix my inventory.
Goddamn inventory here.
It's full.
You know what I need?
I need a chest.
I need a staging area where I have chests where I can just dump all my shit to be sorted later.
That's what I fucking need, because the issue I have, I come home and I'm in the zone, you know?
And I don't want to be sitting there going, oh, where does this go?
Where does that go?
I just want to be able to dump all that shit and move on.
So maybe I'll use this top row for that nut right now.
This is the dumping chest.
Also, click this.
Although the ores and stuff, I know where they go, so put them in here.
Dump time.
Dump, dump, dump.
Dump it all.
In.
In, in, in, in.
Ah, this one I want.
In, in.
Actually, keep this because I think it's redstone related.
Glass wall.
Yeah, sure.
In you go.
This one I want to keep.
Nah, put it in.
I want to keep this.
Bottled water goes in potions, because that's kind of important.
I kind of need to make more bottled water.
I don't have enough.
Uh, fishing.
I don't need four bait right now.
Although put this in the fishing one.
There.
Uh, okay.
We have these baits here.
All right, let's go.
Oh, uh, you're going as well.
Put this there.
Uh, should I be bringing anything else?
Let's think.
Maybe potion of danger sense.
Which one was that?
Let's see if I can see it without looking at the name.
It's... I think it's... I don't think I have one.
It's an orange one and these are the only orange ones I have.
I'll bring one of these.
And I will bring...
What else should I bring?
Maybe I want the battle potion to have more enemies.
For a chance to get that altar or whatever.
Maybe one of these magic power ones, because that's nice.
Life force I want to save.
Let's try this.
See how big of an effect it has.
Lots of bottles.
Builder.
Just the location of enemies.
Okay.
All right, let's go.
Let's kill these fools first.
And let's put on the sounds again.
I forgot what it was at.
It's probably okay.
So it seems like they're not actually gonna keep stacking.
If you don't kill them, they're not gonna keep spawning.
There's a set amount at any given time.
And they're not actually just gonna stack forever.
You know what?
I can probably just leave and they're gonna be fine.
You're gonna be fine, right guys?
I'm closing the doors so they can't get in.
There we go.
And this one as well.
Now where do I want to go?
Oh, perfect.
It's over now anyway.
Beautiful timing.
Uh, there's crimson.
Actually, you know what?
I never did.
Oh, I never did go very deep in the crimson area.
Maybe that's all I need to do.
But wait, there's actually nothing crimson here.
But there is something... maybe I missed something over here, actually.
You know what?
Let's go there.
Let's-a go!
We're off on another adventure.
Okay, I want to jump down.
Here.
Oh, I can't take fall damage.
I gotta remember.
Yes, I cannot.
Let's put this one...
No, let's put... Wait, what did I have here before?
That was...
Was this one?
I guess so.
Alright.
Maybe I don't want that on all the time, because I don't want to use mana potions all the time.
Let's put the thingy on there instead.
Now, let's go down here.
We are on the lookout for a Crimson Altar.
Oh, there's actually a chest down there.
I'm taking that.
I can't see shit.
Ooh!
What?
Locky inner tube!
Look at this!
Sharkbait!
Sandcastle bucket!
Oh, wait, am I in water?
I'm in water.
Hell yeah, man.
Give me all this.
That's kind of nice.
What is this?
Is that a Crimson Altar?
Actually...
Is that what that is?
I've seen these everywhere.
Hold on.
There was something about the hammer.
Oh, no.
Yeah, I take damage from that.
Hold on.
I'm not sure about that.
Let's keep that in mind.
Maybe those are the ones.
Oh, there's actually a chest here.
But I actually want to come back here.
Doll umbrella.
Thank you.
Let me actually put these potions on.
There we go.
All right, let's go.
I want to see, since I'm here anyway, I want to see if there's anything else that I missed here.
Because there's a whole wide area here.
Look at this.
That I didn't explore underneath the Crimson.
What's up, sir?
Oh, it's time to drain.
Hey.
Drain the shit out of this.
Do we have anything else down here?
Oh, wait, we're not in Crimson anymore.
Wait,
is this even Crimson?
This is not.
This is.
I guess I never went here.
You know what?
We're going to be digging anyway.
Let's go.
Go down to the right.
Make a big-ass tunnel here.
Do I even need tungsten for anything anymore?
I have so much of it, man.
Get away.
I defeated your master, stupid slimes.
Don't you dare touch me.
Actually, do I have my... Oh, I do.
Lovely.
Okay, now we're approaching the cave I was in earlier.
This is where I fought the boss.
Actually, I fought it twice, I think.
Killed it twice.
Get some air.
You know what?
Put this on that keybind.
It's weird that the keybinds up there are not showing the ones I've actually bound.
Like, it's not 8, 9, or 0 for me.
I changed it to C, B, R, and B.
So, like, why is that not changing?
You know?
A bit weird.
What's up, dude?
Oh, hello.
Nice.
You know what?
I think these are... these has to be the one.
They have to be the Crimson altar.
Like, actually, I'm so sure of it.
Hold on.
I'm actually gonna...
Wait a minute.
I have an idea.
Where's my potion of return?
Shit, did I... Oh, I did.
Nice.
Maybe that's a bit of a waste on that, because it's not... I wasn't too far away from home.
But whatever.
I don't care.
Okay, these here go up here, first of all.
In you go.
This one gets sold.
This one is shit.
Also gets sold.
This one gets sold.
Everything gets sold.
Now, what were the ingredients?
Fuck.
It was...
It was Jungle Spores.
It was, of course, the tissue sample.
And the last thing was Jungle Spores tissue sample.
I forgot.
Tell me.
Tell me what it is.
The bones.
Right.
Bones.
Now, where did I put the bones?
There it is.
Beautiful.
Got it.
Okay, let's sell real quick.
There we go.
Uh, sell, sell, sell.
Oh, no.
Why can't I shift click here?
Kind of weird.
All right, and then we go back.
Now, watch this.
Watch this be a crimson altar.
What else could it be?
See what I fucking said.
Hey, hey, hey.
How does this work?
Okay, so it's a chest.
And then...
Oh, it's just like, it's just like the money trough.
But this is big, because now I know whenever it says crimson altar, I know where to go.
Oh, shit.
I don't have any mana.
That guy got fucked just now.
Get away from me so I can experiment.
How does this exactly work?
Oh, it's just an extra money trough.
Dude, I'll take it.
Probably I can make more of these void bags.
Oh, wait.
No, I can't.
It says, uh, it's individual to every, uh, user or something, right?
Isn't that the description?
I'm gonna try, though.
I betcha.
Okay, so if I put stuff in here...
Cool sound effect, by the way.
If I put potion of return in here...
And then I go here, it's in there.
And when I open this now, it's a completely different inventory.
Dude, that's awesome.
Dude, this just doubled my inventory space.
Well, actually, it increased by 50%, technically.
But that is amazing.
Well, it did exactly what I thought it would do, and I'm happy about that.
It does everything I ever wanted it to do.
I am a heavy camber.
Please die already.
Thank you.
Now, can I just pick this up anywhere?
Oh, wait.
Of course, I can't destroy that.
So what if I put this here now?
Aha!
That is beautiful!
Okay, now I want to do this.
Now I want to... Actually, since I have... Oh, man.
I know the perfect place to put the void bolt.
I know the perfect place.
I think you know as well, don't you?
There.
That's the place.
Fishing is aligned.
Crate potion is ready.
Let's do that now.
Dude, we are killing it right now.
We are killing it.
Let's fish here in this nice spot.
I'm gonna go up here and fish.
Oh, my god.
Everything is aligning in this game right now.
It feels incredible.
That one.
Haha!
Cheers, everybody.
Happy Friday.
Wait.
Oh, a greater chance.
Not 100%.
Okay.
Hey, here we go.
The first crate has been acquired.
I should have brought that other potion that allows me to see what I'm actually catching.
Not that it matters too much.
Maybe it does.
I'm not feeling that greater chance.
Come on.
What was that?
Oh, quest item?
Do I have a quest from Izzy the Angler right now?
Where he needed me to catch that?
I wonder.
Oh, no, it broke.
Oh, yeah.
Come on, give me some crates.
There we go.
Nice.
More.
Boister.
Man, I love this little house I made.
It's so cool.
Look at the scorpions over there.
Hopefully, they're not poisonous.
I think, man, I would love to live here.
Dude, my dream house is somewhere remote.
You know, like a desert or a mountaintop away from civilization, but still have access to high-speed internet and all that, of course.
Like, all the amazing utilities are present.
And it's like, it looks like a very shitty house from outside, right?
But inside, it's actually super cozy and high-tech.
And then at night, because there's no light pollution, I can... I have a room with like glass, glass ceiling, right?
I can just lie in a couch or whatever and look at the stars.
Golden crate!
Oh, my god.
And then during the day, I'm just gonna sit at my fucking amazing computer and play video games, and enjoying life.
Now, that's the life.
Oh, come on.
I thought I was fishing.
I'm so much on autopilot right now.
Golden crate, three wooden crates and two iron crates so far.
We're gonna have a box opening session very soon.
60 seconds left.
What's up, Hano?
Look at this trophy there.
That's me defeating the king of slimes or whatever.
I like how the slime is on the sword.
It's a good trophy.
I wish I got a trophy from all the bosses I killed, so I could hang them up, have a trophy room.
That's what I want to do.
Okay, I can get two more in, I think, before time runs out.
No, three.
Come on, come on, come on.
More.
More oysters.
Okay, fine.
That was good.
Now, I'm gonna go to the beach and figure out the pylon situation there.
And I'm gonna fish there with a crate buff.
I also want to fish in the jungle with a crate buff.
Uh, no.
There's actually also a crimson place here that I already explored, never mind.
Man, crimson ain't even shit.
This place is easy.
In the beginning, I was scared of it.
I do admit that.
But nowadays, crimson, it's nothing.
Look at that nice tree.
Did I make that?
Did I plant that?
It looks a little out of place.
I'm not sure.
Maybe I did.
Thank you.
And over your money.
I could also fish here, I guess.
But not here.
Oh, I think this counts.
Let's try.
Okay.
Oh, no.
Oh, I forgot the crate buff.
You know what?
No, no, no.
Let's do it at the beach.
Arcane depth meter.
All right.
We should soon be there.
We have to get to the fucked up jungle first.
The jungle that I think is a jungle, but it's not actually a jungle jungle, you know?
That place.
Dude, I'm actually excited to finish my masterpiece on the ground.
That's gonna be so hype.
I'm gonna have my void vault there and everything.
Stupid meteor enemies.
That's my torch.
Accelerate.
That's what I need to have.
I need to have that accessory on me that will allow me to accelerate faster.
Okay, guys.
What's up with the pylon here?
Huh?
You do not sell a pylon.
Is he...
You did it.
You're still in one piece, though.
How boring.
Bro.
All right.
I guess I did take that quest last time.
Uh, why do they not... Okay.
Okay, hold on a second.
What's happening?
Are we okay?
Everything's fine?
Okay.
Uh, wait, why am I... Am I burning?
I am burning!
Huh.
Why was there an icon of the guide right there when I was burning?
That was a little bit creepy.
Okay, let's see what's in here.
Masturbate 3.
I should be looking here, actually.
This is much easier to see what I get.
Obsidian nice sailfish boots.
What is that?
The wearer can run super fast.
Oh, I already have that.
Okay.
Well, thank you.
Anyway.
Spiked stepstool.
Armored tsunami in a bottle.
Flipper potion.
Double jump.
Awesome.
Cool.
What else?
One more tsunami in a bottle.
So many tsunamis.
Masturbate and goodies.
Thank you.
That was lovely.
Now see, this is the time.
So here's the question.
Can I still do this when my void vault is in my gate?
So what's the point of having this?
What's the point of even making this one?
May pick up overflowing items when open.
Really?
What do you... Hmm.
How's that work exactly?
Let's say I put all kinds of crap in here.
Let's say I deposit all.
There.
And I go out here.
And I... Let's say I... Oh.
Yeah.
Let's say I pick up a star.
What happens?
Oh, wait.
That's the... Here.
Oh, no.
They go here.
Never mind.
But wait.
What if I...
Let's say I put the stars here.
Is this overflowing?
Or is overflowing meaning when I have a full inventory?
I need to know the definition of that overflowing.
There.
Let me get that star.
Ah, no.
Okay.
It doesn't work like that.
That would have been sick though.
Oh, I'm on fire.
Wait, did that meteor guy follow me all the way to the beach then before?
Is that what happened?
That would explain how I got hit while in the cellar.
Hold on.
Let me... Wait, where's my... Wait.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, do I need to have it on me maybe?
Wait a minute.
Whoops.
No, don't drop it like that.
Oh, maybe this one physically picks them up because it looks like it's vacuuming.
Look.
It's sort of sucking things in.
So if I were to kill... Okay, starfish.
Put a starfish in here.
Let me get another starfish.
Ah, man.
I was hoping it would automatically sort of just put them in here.
Unless I need to have... Wait a minute.
Unless I need to actually have this put down first.
Is that affected at all?
So let's say I do this.
Put it in here.
Hold on.
What does it say again?
Functions as an extended inventory when open.
Okay, so right now it's open.
May pick up overflowing items when open.
May.
What do you mean by May?
That definitely doesn't pick up.
Okay, I'm not sure.
I am not sure.
I guess I'll just experiment for a while and see what happens.
Oh, yeah, I can't move that.
You know what?
For now, let's put this here.
I kind of like this little... I love this little cellar.
This is the tits.
Mmm.
And look at this cake.
20% in... Whoa.
Holy shit.
I'll be eating of that cake all the time.
I'm going back down here now.
And I'm just gonna drop.
Look at this.
Whoa.
And then we go here.
Let's see.
Where was I here?
Oh, I have the net now.
Hey, you.
Come here.
Come here, you.
Oh, it's afraid of me.
Don't be afraid of me.
Hup!
Come on.
Got it!
Failing!
Let's catch more.
There was more somewhere.
Where was it?
Oh, wait, they disappear.
After a while, I think.
Oh, no, wait, there's liquid in here.
How did that happen?
Uh, it's fine.
It's fine.
Drain.
Yeah.
There we go.
Okay.
The master plan can continue.
Uh, let me, let me think about this now.
How did I intend to do this last time?
Oh, yeah, I had the issue.
I couldn't.
I couldn't transport the liquid from below to top.
Hmm.
How am I gonna do this?
I, I guess I, okay, man, I don't want to say this, but maybe the solution is to simply build it a level lower and try again.
Since the liquid is here now, just build below that level.
And this time, since I know what I'm in for, don't fuck it up.
That would be a way to do it, I guess.
It's a little bit crazy.
Let me actually, why is it so dark here?
Isn't this darker than last time I was here?
This feels very dark.
Let's put torches everywhere.
Let me see if this is even doable.
Let's think about this.
I already sort of have a nice little cutout here we can use.
So it shouldn't take too long either.
And I can use this to drain down this way.
I, you know what, I like it.
I like it.
I like it a lot.
I'm doing it.
It has been decided.
Let's kill these fuckers first.
Is there a trap here?
Victor, who's you?
Who's you?
Oh,
excellent.
Someone's finally come to take some of these maggots off my hands.
Let's see what you've got.
Wand of sparking.
Strange brew.
Purple counterweight.
Bombs.
Oh, you know what?
I'll take 200 bombs.
Wait, hopefully I didn't just... Wait a minute.
Okay, thank God.
I thought I just accidentally used all my money.
That it was more expensive than I thought it would be.
But that's not the case.
Nice to have some bombs.
Come on.
There we go.
What does this do?
Okay, I can do anything.
The detonator goes in
the way.
Got it.
Definitely want to be asking Bradley about that one.
Wait.
Oh, I have to go up here.
Here's the plan.
It's already have this.
This is basically already done for me.
Almost.
So I just continue.
This is lovely.
I don't see any other way to do this.
The bucket was a non-success.
Also called a failure.
Ha!
I was quick.
Whoopee cushion.
Nice.
Time to prank some people.
It's pranking time.
Maybe I can even make a little access path between two areas here.
That would be cool.
This is going to be the most amazing place ever when I'm done with this.
And the best part, there's not going to be any enemies down here during the night.
At least I don't think so.
Well, there's enemies right now, but maybe I'm wrong, actually.
Maybe there will be.
But I doubt there's going to be a blood moon down here.
And I doubt it's going to be raining slimes down here.
Like I just fell in the thing.
He's still there, look.
Is he getting turned into something?
I think he disappeared.
I can't see him anymore.
What the hell?
Okay, so I think this is about a good size for now.
But the thing is, once I finish this, I can't change the size, so I kind of need to be sure.
You know?
Everything is above me now, that's great.
A little more.
Dude, I absolutely love doing this sort of stuff.
It's the best.
Oh, let's be careful here.
Yeah, that's good.
Okay, it seems good, I think.
I don't think it needs to be bigger than this, because otherwise there's just not going to be enough of that liquid anyway.
Put that there.
So here I need my thing, look.
That's how that works.
I have finally figured out that implement.
There it is.
Okay, cool.
Now I need a channel here.
Also, I need a way in, of course.
I guess we make a little tunnel in, if you want to come from the outside, I guess.
Or actually, even better, you got to drop down from the... Oh, can we do this?
Is it doable?
Is it too late now, though?
It may be too late.
But you know what?
If I can make a pylon down here, then that's the answer.
If I can get people to move in and make a pylon down here, it's got to be possible.
It's got to be possible.
And I also want to think here, what should the separation be here?
Probably two blocks is fine, right?
That seems good to me.
Now, can I replace this without draining?
I definitely can.
Good.
There we go.
Nice.
And then we dig up over here.
I'm going to torch.
I'm so afraid of accidentally having the smart cursor on during this.
Yeah, that's good.
And I kind of want it to be sort of a little lake-ish on top.
And then underneath, it's sort of a pipe system, almost.
If that makes sense.
Something is something like that.
It goes here, right?
And then it goes down here, something like that.
And then it's two separation there for the floor.
That's good.
And it goes in here.
I guess we can use this now.
The smart cursor.
Dude, I do wonder what happens if different enemies fall into the liquid.
I don't know how to put random enemies in there that I want to put in there.
I kind of want to do experiments, you know?
This is like unexplored territory, so to speak.
Place these.
Okay.
I think the way inside is only going to be through...
Oh, you know what?
I can make a tunnel.
If I'm smart about this.
Oh, can I though?
Yeah, if I drain from one side.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That should be possible.
Let's say the tunnel is here.
Goes that way to here.
Yeah, that seems good.
And then we have a separator there.
Yep.
There's something like...
I think like this, maybe?
This size?
That could be good.
Why is this so difficult to envision?
Let's be careful not to accidentally drain something here.
Would be an unmitigated disaster.
This is going to be the entrance in case you need to or want to exit this little place to go further down.
Yeah, something like that.
Let's use this.
What is that?
A nice fuck off.
Drain some liquid there.
Get rid of these parts over here.
Do I still have the thing on?
Chisel?
Nice.
Good.
There we go.
This is the entrance.
There.
And then it goes from up here down here.
So the way we drain this, we have to be smart about this.
I guess we just drain.
There's not really much else to it.
It's draining time.
Except, of course, first we gotta... Oh, there's a folder there.
This is where it goes.
And let's say it goes to here.
Like, I can decide where it stops, right?
I guess I can always do this and then expand it later if I need to.
Like, I don't need to necessarily have it all planned out right now.
Something like that.
Let's try it.
Let's fucking try it.
I'm probably gonna get sent down with the thingy now, but that's okay.
Wait a minute.
I'm gonna move these two.
Oh, wait a minute.
This needs to be a little tighter.
Give me that.
All right.
Here we go.
I wanna drain from up here first, I think.
I'm gonna get sent through now.
That's okay.
Oh, maybe not.
Here we go.
It's happening.
Look at that.
Dude, this is so exciting.
Yeah, I'm gonna get sucked in.
That's okay.
Whoa.
Awesome.
This looks cool.
Okay, now we go back.
We gotta go around here.
Okay, let's see.
Bro, part of me wants to loop it all the way around.
But before I do that, I need a way in here.
This is something I have to do first, though.
Right?
This is not gonna...
Yeah.
Something I have to do first.
Let me also do this real quick.
There we go.
Fill that up.
And let's see here.
I do actually want to make this like that, so that we can have a door.
Yeah.
Hold on.
Okay, so what I'm gonna do now, let's make a wall.
Let's make a... Can I make a stone block wall, I wonder?
Let me make some wood.
Ah, please go away.
And then from that wood, we're gonna make a workbench.
Place it there.
And then here.
Stone wall.
Beautiful.
Make a lot of that.
That should be enough.
Wall it up.
What we need here is to have people in here first.
And then somehow get a pylon.
That's the step one here.
Dude, this is a lot of wall.
Let me remove that.
It's annoying me.
There we go.
Okay.
Can I make a stone door?
Oh, Skolancer would be perfect here.
Christ, yeah, let's make one.
Ha ha!
Let's use that in here.
Let's make a... Let's see.
Whoa!
What was that?
Oh, it was a little thingy.
You're dead now.
All right.
How do I want to make it in here?
I kind of want to use a different stone, but you know what?
For now, let's keep it simple.
Keep it simple.
Let's see here.
Make it there, I think.
Is that halfway?
Hold on.
Oh, wait, I'm one off for this to be halfway.
You know what?
I could just do this.
Yeah, let's do that.
And then place one more block above.
Oh, but wait, isn't that gonna...
Maybe it is cool to have a separation of one, but it's also kind of risky if I accidentally destroy.
Yeah, you know what?
Let's not do that.
That's way too risky.
If I accidentally destroy it, then I'm fricked.
I can see that happening on accident.
Yeah, let's keep it like this.
I think it's nice that the top part is a little smaller, so that's nice.
Like that.
And then I want to make certain... Like there, there, there, there.
There.
One, two, three, four, five.
And one, two, three, four, five.
Now, I don't like the separation on these.
The separation makes me unhappy.
There, there.
That's fine.
That is totally fine.
There we go.
And then I'm gonna make more wall here.
And we need doors.
These are just temporary doors for now.
I'm gonna make better doors later.
I need to make some more wood.
And then, one, two, three, four, five, two, three...
Ah, it costs way more wood than I thought.
Gosh, darn it.
Well, you know, I should make some more.
Oh, but I'm running out of... Okay, that's fine.
I can always... I can turn them back around always.
Now, I have one, three, four, five.
Okay.
Now, don't... I'll remove that.
Door here, and we're gonna have door there, here, there, and there.
Let's have a torch.
Let's make it a little symmetric here, like that.
Look at that!
Isn't that cool?
I also want to fix this up here.
I'm not happy with that yet, but it will be fixed in due time.
How am I gonna get to this and fill it up?
Probably with the builder potion!
And this one.
Not enough right now, though, but I don't have the builder potion on me.
And I'm not sure how much of a buff that gives me.
Let me make some basics here.
Table.
Let's make two tables.
Let's have a table there.
And a table here.
Two chairs.
One, two.
There.
And let me actually put this against the wall.
There we go.
This should be a suitable house now, right?
Suitable!
Missing it.
Yeah, okay, so the other ones are not right.
So now, let's see here.
I'm gonna look at my notes now.
Also, speaking of notes,
this will tell me no.
Wait, surface?
Wait a minute, what?
Is this the hello that I'm in now?
It looks a little starry, doesn't it?
On the ground.
Yeah, oh, she wants to be in the jungle.
That makes total sense, actually.
Hey, I put him in the desert, didn't I?
Hey, I put this guy in the desert, too!
I rock!
Dude, maybe that's what unlocks the python.
You need them to be in the right biome.
Otherwise, it won't give you the... Let's check, actually.
Okay, so who did I put up there?
Angler.
Ocean, right?
So he's in the right spot.
But what about...
Who else?
Was it Mort?
Wait, Mortall?
Is this the... No, Fjell.
Where's Fjell?
Oh, okay!
Wait a minute, there was another one I put up there.
Sparkle, right, hold on.
Oh, I thought it was an enemy.
Sparkle?
Party girl?
Am I in the hello right now?
Am I in the hello?
Old man.
The hapless old man carries the burden of a heavy curse.
It's said at night he transforms into a horrific demon which guards the dungeon.
Tavernkeep wants to be in the hello.
I think I'm in the hello right now.
What else could this be, right?
Look at this.
There's stars and shit.
It's like purple and...
Where am I right now?
I'm in purple pink land.
We gotta bring party girl and Tavernkeep down here.
Why are there two stars on him?
Wait a minute, what are these stars?
The guide always offers useful advice and crafting recipes.
His origins and unusual connections to this world remain a mystery.
He's been slain three times.
Okay, I should be using this more.
Failing.
These scintillating fairy-like creatures are born when animals wander into the glowing depths of a shimmer pond.
Oh, so that's how they get made.
Okay.
Holy shit.
Clumps.
Nerdy slime.
I like the nerdy slime.
Ale tosser.
Oh, is that what he's doing when he's attacking?
He's throwing bottles, right?
I saw that today.
He's using this.
Amazing.
Okay, so Tavernkeep and party girl.
Let's bring them down here.
Uh,
fuck.
Uh, there.
Driskin, you can be here.
Can they even make their way down here?
Uh, and then the other... uh, what was it?
Party girl?
There.
Go there.
But hold on, do they even like each other?
Let me see my notes here.
That's something the Beastiary doesn't tell me.
The party girl does not like the merchant.
And the party or the Tavernkeep, what was his name?
Driskin.
Did I talk to Driskin about this?
I don't think he cares either way.
Anyway, let's, uh, try.
Let me walk away.
Nothing.
Hold on.
Maybe I need to go further.
Oh, no.
Uh, fuck.
Oh.
Hey, Beast.
You know, maybe I'll explore here anyway now and give these guys a chance to appear while I'm gone.
Sometimes it takes a while.
It's not always immediately.
A little bit weird.
I'm gonna explore here.
Uh, also my inventory.
Here's the thing.
I'm gonna start using this now.
Let me put this there.
Pause it all.
So now this is full.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm not sure how that... I mean, it's just an extra inventory.
That's how I'm gonna use it, I guess.
Jungle spores down there.
Hey.
Is that a bee or a hornet?
A hornet.
Ancient cobalt helmet.
It increases maximum mana by 40.
Six percent increased magic.
Critical strike chance.
Cool.
I mean, hold on.
What is this?
Five defense.
Increased magic damage.
Isn't this better?
Maybe.
I mean, I don't have to set bonus anymore now, but I'm not really using the space gun that much anyway.
Right?
Let's keep this on for now.
Maybe I'll find other parts of that set, and there will be a set bonus.
So where's this big enemy down here that I need to defeat, huh?
Armored Bessouar.
Immunity to poison.
That seems useful in here.
It's a material too.
Awesome.
Let's put that on instead of the digging.
Heal up.
Okay, what do we got?
My god, please die.
I need to be looking at the traps here.
Dude, I just had an idea.
I can repurpose these things I find here to be homes for NPCs.
And it looks nice already, you know?
Maybe I can just expand on it.
Band of regeneration.
Another suspicious looking.
Let me put this on.
Recall potion.
I have so many of those.
There's the Mona Lisa in the back there.
Beautiful.
I don't know if I want to turn this into a house.
No, it's way too.
No, it's way too close to this anyway.
If anything, I want to space these houses out such that I can use them to teleport all over the world.
You know, I want to space them out like evenly.
So I have somewhere to be at all times.
If I want to be somewhere specific, I can just teleport there.
I think that's smart in the long run.
Oh, I didn't get that.
Oh, I did.
Nevermind.
Piranhas!
I need lights.
What am I supposed to go here?
What are the wholeness?
I'm gonna go down into that cave.
There we go.
And then we switch it back.
Easy peasy.
Dude, at some point, I'm gonna have this whole world explored.
It's gonna be nothing left.
Ow.
Oh, this is a big cave.
Did I just get eight gold?
How?
How did I just get eight gold?
That's a lot.
Everyone gets to die.
Hold on.
Did a thingy appear?
The next time a merchant arrives, I actually want to trade because I have money.
I have the mola.
Dude, it's Friday.
Fucking cheers, everybody.
Whoops.
Wrong button.
I was holding it with one hand.
What are you?
I don't care what you are.
You're gonna die.
Wait, is this honey?
Oh, honey block.
I've seen this before.
Wait, is this... Can I scoop this?
What is this water?
Is this honey water?
What is honey water even?
What the fuck am I talking about?
Is it honey?
That's what I meant.
Oh, we got lava here.
Wait, are we that deep?
I guess we sort of are.
Ah, I see a house.
I'm making my way in there.
Oh, that's a nice looking house.
Oh, look how cute this is.
A godly maze.
Really.
Thank you.
Man, look at how nice this looks.
I wish I had the skills to just sort of make something like this.
Oh, look, they have pillars here to support.
What kind of pillar are they using?
Beams.
I cannot... This is background, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
It is.
Okay, cool.
I feel validated in what I've...
Why is there one of these here?
Wait a minute.
What?
Hold on.
Why can I...
Oh, I... It's like exchange.
I exchanged the silver to be bronze, I guess, or copper, whatever.
But I can be placed.
I can make piles of gold.
That actually looks kind of cool.
Yo, you can totally make a treasure room.
Thank you.
Oh, dude, I want to try... I want to try throwing a life crystal into the shimmer.
Let's... Let's remember that.
In fact, I want to try and throw all kinds of things down there, see what happens.
Man, where is this grand fucking monster I'm supposed to kill down here?
Huh?
Where's that monster?
I mean, I'm just gonna explore until I find it, I guess.
I'm draining.
I be draining.
Whoa!
We're fine.
Don't want to go that way.
Let's go to the right here instead.
What is that place?
Look at that.
Oh, that looks interesting.
Hold on now.
What do we got here?
Oh, is this like granite or marble?
Wait, why can't I destroy that?
It's marble.
But what is that right there?
Oh, we've got those Spartans.
Oh, no.
Mistakes have been made.
Emergency, something.
Block it.
Why can't I?
Oh, no.
That's a terrible idea.
What have I done?
All right, it's fine, whatever.
Nobody will notice that.
Oh, my God.
My inventory is full.
Quickstack, deposit all, and then I'm gonna open this now.
Look at this.
Double the inventory, baby.
Oh, beautiful.
Oh, my God.
That's fantastic.
Hell yeah.
And then I can go like quickstack, and then quickstack.
Oh, my God.
How is this not glorious?
Give me that.
We've got a cave down there as well.
There's actually a bunch of interesting pieces of places here.
I feel like there's more to these marble areas than meets the eye, but I'm not sure what it could be.
Oh, I want to fall in the lava.
Maybe I go... Man, where should I go?
I guess there's this whole area here I want to explore, actually.
And let's... Oh, that's why I couldn't double jump.
I just realized.
Let's put this instead of that for now.
Cerebral mind trick.
Night owl.
Okay, I'm going this way.
Sir.
Oh,
no.
Come on.
Ah, nice.
There's already a cave for me.
Ah, that's special.
Diamonds!
This is big.
I kind of want to make the diamond suit.
Or the diamond dresser.
What's that?
Emerald.
We have, I think, amethyst.
Yeah.
Getting all the gems.
Whoops.
Go, go, gadget, auto missile.
I have so many life crystals now.
I actually forgot what Bradley, or I believe it was Dylan, actually, when he told me about the life crystals, what I could make with them.
Okay, and here, empty.
Oh, I see another one.
Thank you.
I blew him up, and then he fell in lava.
That's brutal.
Okay, we've got lava now.
This is actually interesting.
It's lava and jungle.
Oh, maybe that's where the boss man resides.
Don't fall in the lava, please.
Gets kind of scary.
Why am I going this way?
Let's not go this way.
It's a terrible idea.
Oh, I'm not burning.
Okay, fine.
That's a disaster waiting to happen.
Let me get rid of it.
There we go.
Let's go up here.
Keep digging.
Have they moved in yet?
They have.
Nice.
I'm gonna go back there soon.
Then I'll try and see if I can get a teleporter out of those guys.
Here we go, draining again.
I don't have any party lights, unfortunately.
I somehow managed to put a torch exactly in the right spot there.
That's incredible.
Thank you.
So many live cookies here.
Oh, look at that place down there.
Oh, what's that?
Is that honey?
That looks like a honey... what is it called?
Wax?
Beeswax?
Bees?
You know.
Be home.
Oh, look at that.
And I found something.
What have we got here?
Hive.
Hold on.
Ladiator breastplate.
I didn't even notice I got that.
That's not bad.
Oh, where's my honey?
Sup, bees?
I'm here to fuck up your day, I guess.
And steal all your honey.
I think this... Ah, this is definitely honey.
Look how viscous it is.
I need my bucket.
I need bucket here.
This is how I'm gonna get my honey.
Okay, so I finally found the source for that.
That's awesome.
Oh my god, what am I taking damage from?
Stop it.
Hold on, I actually want to go deeper.
Oh, look how viscous it is.
I want to drain the honey.
No, actually, I don't want to drain the honey.
What am I talking about?
Don't drain the honey.
Okay, I'm gonna come back here with a bucket, actually.
Get up.
Okay, so what's the quickest way here?
Honestly, I think it's walking.
Just walking there.
Where I came from.
Same way back.
Also, let me look at that achievement that I got.
Oh, I can't see the latest.
Ah, shit.
Okay, whatever.
It's probably just discover a beehive or whatever, right?
What's that?
Unpleasant rally.
That's another yo-yo.
Yeah.
A shitty one, though.
Do not want it.
There we go.
Then we go this way.
Let's heal up.
Thank you.
Hornet banner.
Why thank you very much.
Okay, then we go this way.
So here's the plan.
I'm gonna go and hopefully there's gonna be a pylon for me down here.
I'm gonna use the pylon, transport back, grab my bucket, come back, and grab the honey.
There was something big I could make with the honey, and I forgot what it was.
But something really cool.
I'm actually taking a lot of damage here.
Maybe you should calm down.
No!
Yeah!
There we go.
Brute forcing it a little bit here.
Dude, I love these boots so much.
What would I do without them?
Wait, how did I even?
Oh, wait, I got transported down here because I fell through the liquid.
Well, gotta make a way up there anyway, so let's do that.
Could even drain that water.
Hold on now, though.
Ow!
What am I taking damage from?
Hello?
Is it things falling?
Oh, it's probably loose rock.
That's what it is.
100%.
Okay, here we are.
Let me get rid of this.
It's annoying me.
Oh, wait, I can't go in this way.
By the sign.
I gotta go in by the left way.
No, no, no, no!
I cannot control my character today.
Okay.
Here we go.
What's up, people?
You like the dicks?
I can't decide what I... This is all mine?
I'm gonna throw the biggest party by myself.
Ew, it's so drabbiny on the ground.
How can you?
Underground?
Are we not in the Hello?
Whatever.
No wonder Mortol has so many accidents.
You can't imagine how much ale he buys from me.
Finally, some peace and quiet.
As a bartender, this is a luxury.
Okay, so you're happy at least.
Show me the pylon.
Fuck!
Is it because you don't like it here?
Fuck you, Sparkle!
No!
So wait, are we technically in the underground?
I mean, I guess we are underground, but you know what I mean?
Let's try something else, then.
Sparkle, you are removed.
You're no longer living here.
Get out!
You don't like the underground?
Fine.
I know someone who does.
Mortol.
Where are you?
Let's put him here.
Let's go this way now and see if he updates.
Sometimes it does it immediately, other times it doesn't.
It's weird.
A bit further away here.
Why is she not leaving?
Let's get them out of the minimap.
There we go.
Oh, they're still... Bro, I don't understand.
Fuck,
I was really hoping I could make a pile on here, so I had an easy way up again.
Fuck.
Hold on.
Who likes the ocean?
Other than... Let's see here.
What is the hallow, then?
Angler likes the ocean, obviously.
Maybe he just wants to be alone.
Maybe that's enough, actually.
The mechanic likes the snow!
Cool.
Okay.
Good to know.
Uh,
underground.
Dude, the dungeon.
I wonder if I cured the curse, then.
What if I make a home for him there?
Will he appear?
I'm gonna try that.
I'm gonna try and make a home in the dungeon.
Uh, where... Can I... Okay, let's filter by...
Filter by... Oh, nice!
I can even do this.
Ocean.
It's only angler so far, and then a bunch of things I haven't discovered.
Maybe if I leave him there alone.
Maybe that's... Ah, didn't it say two or more people?
Maybe I'm not gonna be able to do that, but maybe I will be able to make something in the jungle.
That's my hope, and that's somewhat close to this place for now.
I'm gonna go back.
Let's empty inventory and sell a bunch of stuff and just take stock.
First, click that.
And then pop up these.
Take all.
Click that.
Click on that.
Ludo.
And quick stack.
Oh, my inventory is full!
Let's sell.
Ludo!
Buy my shit.
Jungle Bad Banner, you can have it.
Uh, you can have that as well.
I didn't use it yet.
Hornet Banner, you can have it.
That one.
Uh, the hive is a material.
You can have that one as well.
That one.
Let's see here.
Wait, I have ancient...
Whoa!
Wait, I have two parts of this set now.
Where exactly did I get this again?
Jungle?
I need one more piece.
And I'm chilling.
I have two of these now.
Let's sell that one.
And what else?
The failing!
Oh my god, let's check this.
I'm so excited.
Bradley, tell me about the failing.
Failing in a bottle.
That's it?
A light source?
Bruh.
I mean, I guess that's cool.
I was hoping something a bit more interesting.
That's okay.
What else did I get?
Let me check these real quick.
Yeah, I can sell this, I think.
Ludo?
Wait, Decor?
Wait a minute.
What was this?
Whoa!
Wallpaper?
Hold on now.
No way.
I can buy wallpaper.
Startled heaven wallpaper.
That would be nice in the cave I made.
Or the little house I wanted to make down there.
Okay, we can have this.
Tsunami in a bottle.
Let me check that one.
I think there's nothing interesting there, but let me check anyway.
Oh, never mind.
What's this?
Oh, right.
No, this is similar to what I have here.
Jump height negates fall damage.
Double jump?
Yeah, this is nothing good, it seems.
All right, that gets sold as well.
Ludo!
Hey, yo, hey, have this one.
Used with paint to color.
Oh, man, I can also color walls and stuff.
Obviously, yeah.
That makes sense.
Now, the step stool, there was something I could use that for.
Something that I remember is interesting.
Yeah, hand of creation.
I want this bad.
I have this, I have that, I have that, but I don't have an architect gizmo pack.
I have no idea how to get it.
Dang.
I want this bad.
Hold up to reach higher.
Man, I want that.
Quick Bessouar, let's see that one.
Adhesive bandage, bleeding, poison and bleeding.
Oh, awesome.
Let's keep that in mind.
I don't think I have an adhesive bandage.
I haven't seen that.
No memory of that.
Oh, nature's gift.
Oh, another one of these.
Speaking of those, what could I do with it?
Now that I have one.
Combine it with a celestial magnet.
Oh, this looks awesome.
Causes stars to fall after taking damage.
Enemies are less likely to target you.
Stars restore mana when collected.
Oh, I don't have putrid scent or star cloak, but this is interesting.
I definitely want to keep an eye on this.
Yep.
Now hive.
Show me the hive.
Abomination!
Summons the queen bee.
I can make a beehive.
I don't know why in the world I would like to make that.
Beemination.
Stinger.
I actually have all this, I think.
No, bottled honey?
I don't have that.
Let me see what it takes to make that.
I probably need a bottle for that, right?
A bottle.
Show me the bottle.
Yo, Bradley.
Nope.
Buttered honey.
Really?
Ah, there it is.
Oh, right.
I remember this now.
I need honey for that.
I was in the same exact spot and I didn't understand what it meant by required objects honey.
I don't have a honey object near me.
But maybe I need to go down into that pool that I found and actually just stand there.
I need to go here and just stand near this, I think.
And then I'm good.
That's how we do it.
Because you know what?
Hold on.
I bet you to make a water bottle, it's gonna say required objects water.
Let's see.
Yep.
Fuck yeah.
I'm right.
Awesome.
So bring empty bottles.
Gotcha.
Cool.
The step stool, let's put it in here.
And then this is the everything chest.
Let's just fucking throw everything in there and then take the ones we need.
This one, that one.
Let's take that one.
That one, that one.
Oh my God.
I end up taking up everything.
That's amazing.
That one.
Jesus.
Oh my God.
Put the stuff.
Let's see here.
Do I have armor, chest or anything?
I also have this.
Put this in here for now.
Wait, I have two of them?
Oh, I have two of them.
Movement speed and defense.
Defense is better.
I want that.
This one goes in here.
This one goes there.
Bottles come with me.
The nature's gift goes in here.
Hold on.
The ruthless flower fire.
What was this again?
This was the arcing one.
The one that went, you know.
And that's the exact sound it made too, by the way.
Speaking of accessories and weapons, what do I actually have?
I have...
Right.
I don't understand this, by the way.
You know what?
I'm going to do more experiments with that.
Experiments.
Because it says 100%.
It's got to be something.
I haven't really tried this either.
There's a quacking sound.
Water bolt.
Or any of these materials.
I kind of want to experiment with new weapons a little bit.
Even though I love the ones I have.
All right, this looks fine.
Flame lash.
Right, this was the same thing I had, but just fire.
Which could be good against bees, I guess.
Isn't that what you do with beehives?
You fucking burn it.
Now, oh, the honey dispenser.
Wait a minute, honey.
Honey dis... I wonder...
You know what?
I think I should bring this.
Maybe I need this next to...
Hold on a minute, actually.
I wonder if I can put this next to honey blocks, and it will actually dispense honey from them.
Let's try something here.
Let's do that.
And let's grab some honey blocks.
I need to experiment a little bit.
Or maybe even hive.
Grab hive and... Wait, where's my...
Let's see here.
Take all and then click this one.
Open that.
Okay, this one's empty.
Nice.
Now open this one again.
Wait, where's all my money?
Wait a minute.
Where's all my money?
Oh wait, I have a platinum.
Oh, that's why.
I was like, I only have six gold.
It makes sense.
All right, fine.
Okay, everything's fine.
I need to grab honey.
Where is it?
Honey...
It's yellow.
Can't be that hard.
Organic?
Honey block.
There it is.
Let's see here.
Just try that for now.
Oh my, look at this.
I'm actually sort of moving slowly on it.
Look.
It's sticky.
Oh, wait, no.
Oh, nevermind.
Yeah, this makes honey items, not actual honey.
Nevermind.
This is like a crafting bench for honey.
That's what it is.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, I'm pretty sure what I need to do anyway.
I just got to go down there and craft it while I'm standing there.
So there it is.
Bottles I have.
Perfect.
Hive, I can leave here.
And the honey block is organic.
In you go.
What's that?
Rich Mahal, delete that, because there's only one.
The imp staff.
It's kind of interesting.
You know what?
I'm going to take a quick break, because I need to take a piss, and I'll continue.
I'll be right back.
All right.
Okay, I want to go back to the honey now and grab myself some honey.
And on the way there, I'm actually going to bring something more.
I want to experiment throwing things in the shimmer.
And the things I want to throw in are live crystal.
Oh, bring the bucket as well, actually.
Let's just try a bunch of different...
Let's go a little nuts here.
What could be interesting?
Let me try that.
And maybe that one.
One of these.
Let's try a mana crystal.
Summons the blood.
Let's try one of those.
I tried the voodoo doll, didn't do anything.
I tried this one too.
What about a book?
Maybe that will produce a nice book.
A real page turner.
Let me grab these as well, actually.
I kind of need them.
Good to have when you go caving.
Let's see here.
What else should I be throwing in?
Maybe I want to try some weapons.
Let me just try some different stuff.
Oh, there's sticky bombs in here for some reason.
They're not supposed to be there.
Wait, where's my best maze, actually?
I had a better maze than that somewhere.
Is it over here?
Didn't I have a... godly maze?
No?
Pretty sure I had a flaming one that was kind of insane.
I mean, I have it somewhere, I think.
Oh, we also have all of the... You know what?
Bring this one.
This is nice to have.
It makes me run fast.
Let me try...
Let's fucking throw a lawn mower in there.
Why not?
Sharkbait?
Let's just try a bunch of shit.
What about an ancient gold helmet?
You know?
What about this one?
What about... yeah, sure, that's fine.
Okay, that seems good.
Is there anything else I should bring?
Oh, give me the potion of fishing.
Because I do want to go fishing again.
It's weirdly addicting to fish in this game.
Let's see... Sonar potion.
Just one of those, please.
Thank you.
All right, off we go.
Hello.
Fuck off.
I could have just transported.
I'm an idiot.
Never mind.
I forgot about that.
Oh, see, now I can do this.
Put this here, and now we move super fast.
Much better.
Look at that.
Oh, that's a significant bump.
Although when you lose momentum, it's kind of painful, so you gotta be not losing momentum here.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Man, I wonder how I can change my spawn location, if I'm even able to.
I would kind of like to change it, such that I always appear in my house there, instead of to the left of the house, you know?
Look how fast I am now.
I maintain the momentum.
Still got it.
Let's fish in the jungle a little bit.
Froggy!
Where's my... Oh my god, he fell to the bottom of the earth.
All right, you're not worth it.
Where am I going again?
Right.
Yeah, okay, so let's first go to the shimmer, because that's on the way.
We try those things, and then after that, we go grab honey.
That's the plan.
And I don't want to fish right now, because it's nice, and it sucks during the night.
But then again, maybe there are some things that can only be caught during the night.
Wouldn't surprise me at all, if that was the case.
I don't want to exclude any possibility here.
Why is that fallen star that color?
I got a fallen star just now, and it was purple.
Is it always purple?
Wait, why do I have... Wait a minute, this is a material.
I don't think I've tried giving this to Bradley.
I should try that next time.
We are pretty much there.
Let me just quickly check on the ocean here, see if they actually sell a pylon miraculously.
Now that party girl is gone, maybe that's what it took.
Okay, let's see here, no, nothing.
All right then, whatever.
This is so silly.
This is kind of a mess, this place here.
I fucked this up, didn't I?
This is a real mess.
Ah, you're too quick for me.
Gotcha.
Oh, there's more.
I'm gonna grab him.
I'm gonna try throwing one of these inside the shimmer.
How about that?
Okay, let's see here.
Let's throw an ancient gold helmet.
It becomes just a gold helmet.
Whoa.
Wait, I forgot the stats of the previous fuck.
I can throw this shit in.
Oh, wrong one.
Come on.
Nothing, okay.
Sharkbait.
Lawnmower.
Cascade.
Book.
Bloody tear.
Mana crystal.
Oh, arcane crystal.
Yo.
No.
What?
I need to be doing that.
Bro,
that's a biggie.
What the fuck?
Dude.
Dude, this really is way bigger than I thought it would be.
A suspicious looking eye.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, did I throw all of them in?
Whoops.
Black lens.
Nothing.
A bomb?
Oh, what if I throw it like that?
Oh no, I'm an idiot.
Yeah, don't throw bombs right here.
This is a stupid idea.
But you can throw them like... Let's see here.
What about sunflower?
Let's try this.
Probably nothing.
Let's try one tissue sample.
Nothing.
A bone.
What about bait?
I want to try throw a weapon in.
I don't want to throw this in though.
Oh, maybe I should.
Fuck it.
Go.
Nothing.
Life crystal.
Oh, nothing happened.
Vital crystal.
Oh my god.
That's amazing.
How much better though?
Oh shit, I turned all of them into...
Oh no, that's not what I wanted to do.
What about a mechanics rod?
This is the metafishing.
We're throwing the whole fishing pole in the water.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Okay.
What else can I try?
Is there anything else on me that I would like to try?
Link route, maybe?
I don't think anything's gonna happen there.
These are gonna get disassembled into their constituent parts, I'm pretty sure.
What about... No, it's gonna get disassembled for sure.
What about a bottle?
One vertebra?
Did I try that already?
All right, let's grab all the items.
Whoa, nice.
Okay, well, definitely paid off to experiment with that.
Gotta do more of that.
Okay, now guys.
Oh!
A cavern pylon!
It is confirmed, I think.
You need people who like the underground.
No, but wait a minute.
Driskin doesn't like the underground.
Does he?
Wait a minute now.
Clear filters.
How do I clear?
Clear the filters!
There we go.
Tavern keep.
No, he likes the hallow.
Fuck, I'm not sure, man.
What do you have to say?
Ah, no one around.
I can test new bombs without creating a graveyard for limbs.
Dwarves are naturally drawn to the underground.
It's in our blood.
Wait till you see me in action.
Grab it.
Let's put it...
Why can't I put it here?
You can only place one per type and in the matching...
Oh, wait a minute.
Am I not in the underground?
Am I technically not in the underground?
Because this is like the cosmos or whatever?
Hold on.
Let me try something.
What?
Why doesn't this work now?
Disappointing!
What?
Why not?
Why doesn't it work?
Motherfuckers!
They're talking about beer.
He's talking about mice and digging.
He's happy.
All right.
That's the... I don't know why that doesn't work right now.
I'm sure there's a very reasonable explanation for all this.
Okay, let's continue with the original quest for now.
I want to go down and grab me some honey.
Right there.
I have bottles with me.
Let's go.
Go to the left.
Go down here.
Wait, is this technically honey?
Wait a minute.
Oh, I think it is.
Hold on.
Hold on now.
Bottled honey!
Improves natural healing for a short time.
Yo!
Let's just make a shit ton of this.
Throw this away.
That's the leads.
Oh, did I pick it up?
Hold on.
Is there anything else I can do while I'm near the honey?
I can make this, but I don't want to make that.
What if I throw the Fenda metal in the honey?
Probably nothing, right?
Ah, well.
Ah, what else did I want to do down here?
Fuck.
What is that up there?
Oh, it's another one of these.
Let's go in here.
Oh, look.
Honey's falling.
Oh, we've got a big batch of honey.
That's what that's actually so cool.
The honey pool down here was sort of indicative of something being above.
That's awesome.
Let's drain the honey.
We're emptying this hive.
Oh, god.
Oh, hold on now.
What is that?
Oops.
Oh, no.
Oh, I regret all my decisions.
I regret it all.
Okay, I guess we're fighting now.
I need lights.
I can't see shit.
I'm not ready for a fight.
Kill it.
Oh, god.
I can do this.
It's not too bad.
Come here.
Hey, bastard.
This has to be the big boss that we're talking about in the jungle.
Hey, come here.
Give me a big crit.
There we go.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, god.
I'm losing HP here.
Uh-oh.
Let's get rid of all these little ass here.
Oh, no.
I need to heal.
I need to drink that bottled honey.
Oh, no.
Nice.
I just avoided that attack.
You saw that?
Oh, I'm stuck in the honey.
Hey, sir.
I'm totally gonna die here.
I'm dying here for sure.
Yeah, I'm so fucking dead.
30 seconds until healing.
There's no way.
He's shooting things at me.
Come
on, kill it.
Ah, fuck you.
Oh, I dropped all my gold.
God damn.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, well.
No, I wasn't even ready, man.
All my shit here wasn't even equipped.
It was terrible.
I should have had my... Well, I guess this one on.
I guess poison.
Did I get poisoned at all?
That would be the place to get poison, right?
Anyway, let's click this button.
And I kind of want to get back there and kick some ass now.
What's the sound I'm hearing?
Samson, the nerdy slime!
He's having a bath.
Uh, I'm sorry, but will you stop that?
Because you're actually fucking annoying.
You're making an annoying sound.
Samson, you're here.
Let's go.
Come on.
Maybe I need to... Hold on, let me get out of range.
Bro, this is so... Sometimes it works.
Sometimes it doesn't, I swear.
Anyway, I guess I kind of want to go back there and kick ass right now, because I was not prepared at all for that fight.
At all.
That was a bit unexpected.
This is driving me nuts, that sound!
Fucking hell.
Now, why didn't this work?
Can I put it... I guess I can't put it here.
Oh, wait a minute.
No, unequip it.
Oh, I forgot about this.
You can only have one?
Oh, so hold on.
Rosalva doesn't actually like to be here anyway.
She wants to be in the jungle.
I'm not in the jungle right now.
Am I?
This is... I wonder if this technically counts as jungle.
I don't know what this means.
Living wood.
I feel like that's the place she would want to be, no?
She's all about that living wood.
Right?
Hmm.
Maybe not.
I don't know.
You know?
Also, yeah, nevermind.
I'm gonna go... Man, I want to figure out the ocean pylon.
That one is... that's the big one, because it takes me forever to get there.
But then again, if I can get a pylon down in the cave there...
You know what, guys?
I gotta be honest here.
I'm not feeling this right here.
The experiment was not successful.
I gotta say, the design was more grandiose in my mind than it turned out to be.
I am not happy with what I have done.
Sometimes you gotta take the L, and I think I'm gonna do that now.
That will not be a place to be.
We will have a place here, but not there.
This will be abandoned.
Yeah.
I'm not feeling that place, man.
It's too much work, and it's not looking as great as I thought it would.
Samson!
I will murder you!
Fuck you, Samson.
Get drained.
You can jump around down there.
Have fun.
Come
on.
Oh my god.
Please destroy this part as well, will you?
Bro, you are pissing me off.
Are you still gonna make sound down there while I'm up here?
Much better.
Silence.
Amazing.
The cascade.
You can have it.
You know what?
You can have these as well.
Sunflower.
I kind of want to place that.
Why not?
Looks nice.
There we go.
Do I not have a... Oh, I do.
Okay.
Spelunker?
That's nice.
I have two of these now, which is... One of them can be sold, actually.
Ludo.
Here.
That's for you.
Michelinius.
Put the lens in there.
Then a gold helmet.
And then we have all the Michelinius stuff that we took out for experimenting.
Oh, I forgot to try the buckets on the honey.
Shit.
I could have maybe made a little honey pool here, so I could always fill up my honey stuff.
Speaking of honey stuff, bottled honey.
Remind me what I could do with it.
Fuck!
Let's do it!
Uh, let's do it.
Where did I...
There.
Crafting.
I need stinger, hive, honey block.
Stinger, hive, honey block.
Honey block.
Uh, stinger.
And then construction.
Shh, hive.
Where are you?
Hive.
There we go.
Uh, whoa, whoa, wait.
What did I need to craft it?
Which bench do I need?
None.
Oh.
All right.
Make two of them.
In case we fail.
Okay, uh, let's fucking try it.
But first, let's prepare.
Let us prepare for the fight to hit.
I should lay any of this in here.
Uncles, boars, stinger.
All of that construct.
Ah, go in here.
Now, potions.
Let's see.
Mana potion.
Let's see here.
Maybe one of these.
Uh, I think I want this as my preferred potion.
One of these.
Magic power.
Thorns.
Let's do this one.
And that one.
Ah, you know what, maybe I'll save this.
That boss didn't seem that hard.
And this is kind of a nice one.
All right.
Uh, gear.
Let's see.
Movement speed is nice, I guess.
But then again, this one is also... no.
Did I take poison damage from that fight?
You know, maybe I already have what I need here.
This is actually pretty good.
I like that.
I do like that.
Um, here we go.
Oh, wait, statue and shit.
Where did I put all that?
Miscellaneous, maybe.
Where did I put the statue?
Oh, it's already here, never mind.
But then I also had the thing I could hang from the ceiling.
Man, I have no idea where I put that.
That's gonna be almost impossible to find, I think.
Also, I lost a lot of gold.
I gotta go collect that.
Shit, I kind of forgot about that.
Wait, no.
Wait, why is that in here?
Flinks?
That's fine.
Put this in the miscellaneous.
Shit, where did I put that?
Uh, it's gotta be in here.
But wait, I can make one of those myself, no?
Maybe I did hang it somewhere here.
Tell me again, what's with this?
It was.
Wait a minute.
Paired life crystal?
Life crystal boulder?
What?
I just need chain, I have that.
Thank you.
Let's make a couple.
I guess I can just craft them down here.
One, two.
Hang one.
There we go.
And this is looking mighty fine.
Let's try it.
Oh no.
Oh, why didn't I?
Wait, maybe I have to be in a... Oh shit, I think I have to be in a hive.
Hold on, let's hurry while I have the buffs.
Crap!
Oh my god, come on.
I think we have to be inside the hive.
A burger!
There's just a burger on the ground there.
Major improved?
Wow!
That's actually right, I needed one of those as well.
So I'm gonna eat that before that fight.
Oh, you know what I'm gonna do, actually?
I'm gonna bring a bunch of life crystals and mana crystals to the shimmer as well.
And see how much I can buff?
Probably it's just as much as what I've already done with the normal versions, but it's just gonna give me the region.
And there's a cab on that, I assume.
But I'm gonna do that next time, because I forgot to do it.
In fact, it's actually a good idea that we go back anyway, because I need to pick up my money.
I had 70 gold or something.
It was a lot.
I'm so slow!
Momentum!
I almost need to make a highway for myself, for my walking, so I don't get interrupted.
I even have the speed, it's still so slow.
I really need this pylon up and running.
Did I bring it?
At least.
I did.
Awesome.
For now, I guess I can put it... This will not work here, right?
I'm technically on the ground right now.
No way!
Wait, what?
Is that really true?
Hold on.
What if I'm up here?
I can't place it here then, right?
Wait a minute!
Ah!
Oh!
Okay, never mind.
I was about to say.
Even here, I'm technically on the ground.
Okay, okay, I see.
All right, I was about to say that seemed a little broken.
All right then, cool.
Let's head down again.
We still have buffs, so let's hurry a bit.
Whoops.
Here.
Now, where was it exactly?
Oh, I see it now, I see it.
It's over here.
There it is.
That is where I died.
Is there no way for me to get this boss back without... Oh, 20... Wait.
I had more gold.
Where did it fall?
Over here?
Where's the rest of my gold?
Is it gone?
Why is it gone?
What the fuck?
Ah, it works!
Beautiful.
Let's go.
What you got?
Okay, so there's this face where she just sort of lies around like that.
Fucking bob and weave, bob and weave.
And then she's going to do this.
Oh my god, I killed these small things.
Come on.
Get rid of the small ones.
There we go.
Ah, I shouldn't have jumped there.
Too late.
There we go.
Not too bad.
Do your thing.
Oh my god, she's shooting fast now.
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
Sting operation.
Fucking did it.
Hell yeah, dude.
Another one bites the dust.
That feels amazing.
I kind of want to kill this guy.
Come here.
There we go.
And what did I get?
Man-eater banner.
Okay.
Who's a man-eater?
Treasure bag.
Rash hive pack.
Increases the strength of friendly bees.
Expert.
Places hives.
Say whoops.
Consumes hive.
Oh, I don't have any hive on me.
Hold on, let me try.
Oh.
What is the difference between that and just placing it manually?
Oh!
B-wax!
Oh wait, did I get that from... Oh, maybe I got that when I killed the boss.
Never mind.
Yeah, yeah.
B-nade?
12 range of damage.
Extremely weak, explodes into a swarm of bees.
Let's try.
Holy shit.
Let's try again.
Oops.
And they just fly around and kill everything.
That's actually pretty good, I guess, for crowd control or killing a bunch of enemies.
We have bee pants.
Let's put on the bee pants, because why not?
What else did we get?
The hive pack.
Oh wait, friendly bees as in from the bee nade.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I have a great idea.
I'm gonna go to the shimmer.
I want to try and throw a bee nade in there, because I need to see what it's made of.
I kind of want to craft it myself, if you know what I mean.
I don't know why I said it in that way.
There's no weirdness behind that.
It really just is me wanting to craft it, I swear.
If you know what I mean.
Go this way.
Ah!
I'd be stuck.
For now, I'm gonna make a temporary... Let me actually cut through here.
I'm gonna make a temporary...
What?
Oh yeah, I also got this.
But that's not what I was looking at.
I was...
I think I understand what's happening here, guys.
So, what does it say even?
Someone's killer bees after striking your foe.
When the text, when I pick something up, is purple?
Like, look at this.
Mud block.
I was about to say that looked different.
So, okay.
So, cool.
When my inventory is full, it's just gonna fill it up with shit.
That's pretty damn good, dude.
I'm gonna put this here for now.
There we go.
This should work.
Hey!
Fuck yeah.
Now, quickly go back.
Oh my god, that's so far.
Oh man, what a convenience this is.
Maybe I do like this after all, guys.
By the way, this is kind of cool.
I'm not finished yet, either way.
You know what?
I'm not giving up on this dream, damn it.
I'm not.
I shall make this into a glorious sprawling place.
Oh wait, I need to go here.
Okay, let's see here.
Be... Nade.
Ah.
No!
I'm okay.
Back up.
Okay, now.
Be... Nade.
Ah!
Be waxed like grenades!
No, no, how to make it?
Oh, wait a minute.
Be wax.
How do I get be wax?
Maybe I just have to kill a bunch of queen bees.
Also, let me try this a bit.
This is like the whole bee fucking set here.
Bee at...
Sorry, bee melee weapon.
And then we have a bee nade.
And a rash hive pack.
So this summons killer bees after striking a foe, right?
The bee nade summons killer bees.
And if I wear this, it's gonna make him even better.
Uh... fuck, put it here, I guess.
So that's nice.
I actually want to try this.
Let's see how good this is.
Hey!
Oh, what's happening here?
This is actually a shortcut to get down, look.
Oh no!
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Wait, I need to make an air pocket.
It's fine, it's fine.
Air pocket, there we go.
Look, we're fine, we're fine.
Oh my god, that was scary.
I guess I could have just teleported... you know what?
What am I even talking about?
Just fucking do that!
I'm panning in these situations, dude, and I can't think clearly.
No.
Now, I want to see bee wax.
Let me see here.
Bradley!
Talk to me.
Tell me about the bee wax.
High five!
Dude, I gotta.
Wait, I don't have enough?
Oh no, I don't...
We need to summon more queen bees.
We need to summon all the queen bees, kill them all, gather the beeswax, and create the ultimate bee armor.
I shall become the master of bees!
I'm gonna write that in my notes.
Become master of the bees.
Exclamation mark.
Fuck yeah.
Heck yeah, dude.
All right.
Bradley, I'm not done with you.
Now, show me again.
So this one summons killer bees.
I want to make this whole set.
And I also want to make this.
And I want to make this... I want to make them all!
I actually want to make this first, I think.
So here's what I think, by the way.
Oh, no, wait, this has hornet.
It doesn't say bee, so what I'm thinking...
Uh, wait a minute, where's this thing I had?
This one increases the strength of friendly bees.
I don't think this means the hornet that is mentioned here.
I think it means the bee spawned from the bee nade or the bee spawned from the hurtful beekeeper.
That's what I think.
Because this is a hornet and that's a different thing.
All right, so there it is.
But let me actually try to make one of these things.
Dude, I want to become the ultimate... I want to summon a million bees.
You know that meme with, uh, with like Oprah?
She's like, and now bees!
And there's just bees everywhere.
It's one of the funniest fucking gifts that have ever been made.
Incredible.
That's what I want to become.
I want to become Oprah.
Guys, I want to become Oprah.
But to become Oprah, you need to eat a lot of food first.
And I don't mean it in that way.
I just mean I need to eat now because I'm hungry.
So the Oprah-fication happens next time.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
What's up, people?
Opening chat.
Oh, wait, I don't even have the window open.
Hold on a second.
And there we go.
What's up, guys?
Great stream, Oliver.
Thank you, Northstar.
And thanks for becoming a straight line.
I appreciate it.
Welcome, welcome.
This has been so entertaining.
I'm glad you like it, cornflake.
I've had a blast today.
This game never fails to entertain me.
I'm having a great time.
Become Oprah.
Don't even need to change the logo.
Maybe I don't get that.
I don't understand that.
Does Oprah have a logo?
Similar to mine?
Does she have a logo?
What a good stream today and nice work clearing out that bee infestation.
Thank you.
Fuck yeah.
Makes me happy.
Awesome stream, some good smarts and some good face palm moment.
You know, you need both to balance things out.
In the end, the universe tends to unfold as it should.
And that requires things to be in balance.
You can't have too many good things.
You need to balance them out with the bad.
Or not bad, just not as good things.
Perfect five out of seven.
Love it.
That's also a meme, isn't it?
Is that an old one?
I feel like is that from 15 years ago, Jen?
Nice job killing Queen Bee.
Hope the shimmer house turns out well.
Yeah, me too.
It's gonna be great.
Dragonfire 973.
I don't usually get to catch it live, but love the playthroughs.
Thank you so much, man, for saying that.
Makes me happy.
The first letter of Oprah's name is O.
Oh, of course.
Man, sometimes I am a little bit slow.
I'm sorry.
Maybe in Danish it's spelled Oprah.
It's actually not.
Oliver, did you end up getting the XDXXS 440?
I have no idea what you're talking about, Jen.
What is Jen even talking about, guys?
Good job finding the crimson altars.
Yes!
I know, right?
That one has been bugging me for a long time.
Trying to figure out what that was.
Are you gonna play modded Terraria?
Not in this playthrough.
Maybe in the future, who knows?
But it's gonna be the same kind of promise as when I said I'm gonna play Terraria modded.
It's also in the future.
I mean, it's one thing to play the game first, but there's so many other games also.
It's gonna be one of those times when I'm feeling the Terraria, you know?
Like, I've had moments where I'm like, damn, I really want to play as a Minecraft within the last couple months, you know?
And that would be perfect to jump back in with some mods.
Stuff like that.
Almost flooded this shimmer house with that bomb.
Yeah, that was a bit... that was a wake-up call for me.
I was like, calm down a bit here.
Think about your actions before you do it.
Have you heard about Void Stranger?
I think you'll like it.
Good stream, as always.
Hey, Shu, I have not heard of Void Stranger.
I've heard of... is it called Void of the Dark or something?
That's probably not the same thing.
I'm gonna write it down.
Void Stranger.
I'm guessing it's a game, right?
We've been talking about you finding the Crimson Altars for a while.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Well, now I know where they are, at least.
That's nice.
You mean Minecraft, right?
You said... Oh, yeah, probably did, yeah.
Hypnogry.
Hypnogry?
How do I pronounce your name?
Is it Hypnogry or... Hypnogry?
Oh, by the way, Oliver, what's the schedule for inscription gonna be?
Uh, as often as I can, basically.
The thing is, I have a lot of work these days, so even just getting this in today has been a little bit... like, I'm blasted today.
So I'm trying to get as much done as I can and upload as often as I can, hopefully every day.
Yeah, but sometimes, maybe not.
The thing is, I sometimes like to have a little backup of episodes, so they're ready, because there are times when I just can't play any games for a period.
So I need to have some for those days, you know, to balance things out a little bit.
Oliver, would you choose to live in an isolated forest cabin with all the amenities?
Yes, I would.
100%.
That sounds awesome.
Clearly, Oliver needs to play Serial Ranger.
I haven't heard of any of these games, guys.
What the fuck?
I mean, I have a whole list of games that I'm intending to play, by the way.
You can check them out on the Discord.
If you join the Discord and go to the games channel, there's a pinned post where I have put all the games in no particular order that I want to play in the future.
So check that out.
Anyway, I gotta eat, because my stomach is growling.
So it's time to get some grub.
And as always, I gotta go get to the store first, because I always have an empty fridge for some reason.
Okay, guys, I will be out of here.
Thank you so much for watching.
I've been having fun.
Enjoy your Friday and enjoy your weekend, okay?
Have a good one.
Goodbye.